YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.net
■
时间轴：   YY
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： Vero  非燕  阿蘅  一块二  独醉
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY    后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第一集
孩子们  在我们快要接近结局
Kids, if there's one big theme to this story--
却又没那么快结尾的故事中
and I swear, we're totally, almost,
有一个贯穿始终的主题  就是机缘
not really all that close to the end-- it's timing.
机缘至关重要
Timing is everything.
比如  如果不是去参加婚礼
For example, I never would met your mother
我就不会遇到你们的母亲
if it weren't for a wedding.
那场最出乎我意料的婚礼
The last wedding I ever thought I'd be at.
你觉得这条领带如何
What do you think of this tie?
感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
我还以为巴尼・史丁森在婚礼前的召唤
Barney Stinson needs you right before his wedding,
是让我帮他处理藏在衣橱里的妓女尸体
you assume there's at least one dead hooker in the closet,
对不对啊
right?
这条有好一点吗
Is this one better?
这条领带棒极了
Look, the tie is great,
你只是在婚礼前有点小紧张
And, you know, it's perfectly normal
这种现象很正常
to have some pre-wedding jitters.
我不是紧张
I'm not having jitters.
我只是想到  一旦我系上这条领带
It just occurs to me that once I put this tie on,
就不能摘掉了
I can never take it off.
我就得一生一世系着它
I have to wear this tie forever and ever.
虽然这条领带现在很苗条
And sure, this tie's skinny now,
万一它变胖了  对我呼来喝去怎么办
but what happens if it gets fat and starts bossing me around?
我会不会做了个错误的决定
Did I make a mistake?
要是系别的领带  我会更开心吗
Would I have been happier with the other tie?
泰德  我能告诉你个天大的秘密吗
Ted, can I tell you a big secret?
当然
Yeah, of course.
我说的其实不是领带
I'm not really talking about the tie.
我明白  巴尼
No, I got that, Barney.
我在想这整件事会不会是场灾难
I wonder if this whole thing's a disaster.
如果变成史上最烂的婚礼怎么办
What if this is the worst wedding ever?
不可能
Not possible.
我们已经参加过史上最烂的婚礼了
We've already been to the worst wedding ever.
小粉拳的婚礼
Punchy's wedding.
马修简直把它毁得一干二净
Marshall really took a two flusher on that one.
马修叔叔毁了
The story of how Uncle Marshall ruined
我朋友小粉拳婚礼的故事
my friend Punchy's wedding
发生在2011年9月
starts in September, 2011.
小粉拳邀请我做他的伴郎
Punchy had asked me to be his best man.
各位  走之前你们介不介意
Guys, before we go, would you mind
听我读一遍婚礼致辞
reading my wedding toast?
-没问题  -当然可以
- Oh, yeah, no problem. - Sure.
好吧  反正没得选
Um, all right, if I have to.
好吧
All right.
人家准备了各种不同的版本嘛
There's a few different versions.
泰德  你干嘛这么大费周章地写祝词
Ted, why are you working so hard on this toast?
人家小粉拳是在保龄球馆
Punchy belched his proposal
随便拿个唱K的话筒求的婚
through a karaoke mic at a bowling alley.
好吧  我从没跟你们说过
Okay, look, I've never told you guys this,
但这几年来  我一些高中旧友
but over the years, a few of my old high school buddies
纷纷邀请我在婚礼上致辞
have asked me to give wedding toasts,
结果场面都不太好看
and they haven't gone great.
不知怎地  那些婚礼恰恰
Somehow those weddings all fell smack-dab
碰上了我人生最悲剧的时刻
in the worst moments of my life.
琼尔和莫拉的爱情是美好的
Joel and Mora's love is a beautiful thing.
我原以为我也拥有
I thought I had that...
结果我的未婚妻上周在圣坛上离我而去
till my fiancee left me at the altar last week.
他们不让我说起这个  所以我就不说了
I was asked not to talk about this, so I won't.
我有时夜里会坐在她家门外
I sit outside her house at night sometimes.
她剪头发了
She got a haircut.
上周我失业了之后
After I lost my job last week,
他们就不让我宣读祝词了
uh, I was asked not to give this toast...
不  我要说
No, no, no!
幸福的夫妻需要听到这句话
The happy couple needs to hear this.
好花不常开  好景不长在
Things end.
就数据统计而言 你俩很可能离婚
But from the ashes of your statistically
然后形影单只  孤独终老
probable divorce,
但枯木终逢春
hope can rise anew.
因此我准备开创我自己的建筑公司
That is why I'm starting my own architecture firm--
莫比斯设计公司[Mosbius 法国国宝级艺术家]
Mosbius Designs.
莫斯比设计公司关门大吉
Mosbius Designs has failed.
三个月后
但是艾利克斯和杰西卡的爱情  提醒着我们
But Alex and Jessica's love reminds us that...
我的天
Oh, God!
尿斯比经典时刻
Classic Schmosby.
小粉拳把你人生的低潮期都放在网上
Whoa. Punchy posted the low points of your life online?
没那么简单
Oh, not just that.
莫斯比设计公司  关门大吉 *
* Mosbius Designs has failed
但是艾利克斯和杰西卡的爱情  提醒我们 *
* But Alex and Jessica's love reminds us that...
我我我我们 *
* Tha-tha-tha-tha-tha...
我的天
Oh, God!
所以现在我在所有高中旧友的心目中
So now I seem like a total train wreck
就是一个彻头彻尾的倒霉鬼
to all my old high school friends.
在芬兰还有一群见证者
And a bunch of people in Finland.
那个混音视频在他们那儿引起了不小的轰动
The auto-tune thing got kind of big over there.
所以我必须要搞定这次致辞  华丽转身
That's why I have to nail this toast.
泰德  无论你想在婚礼上搞定什么
Ted, you want to nail something at this wedding--
必须先扔掉这大部头
lose the Trapper Keeper.
你唯一需要带去克利夫兰的东西
The only thing you need to bring to Cleveland
就是这个
is this.
那年秋天  我成了纽约史上
That fall I became the youngest architect
最年轻的把摩天大楼炸为平地的建筑师
in the history of New York to break ground on a skyscraper.
流行杂志专门为我做了个特辑
Which led to a glowing magazine feature.
我打算把它裱起来
I planned on having it framed--
巴尼叔叔的计划却与我背道而驰
Uncle Barney had different plans.
你的致辞要这么念
Here's your toast--
"女士们  要签名请排队  谢绝肥妞"
"Single file, ladies. No fatties"
这太荒唐了
That's ridiculous.
是啊  你说得没错  那儿可是克利夫兰
Yeah, you're right. It's Cleveland.
那就"女士们  要签名请排队"
"Single file, ladies""
我才不要在小粉拳的婚礼上
I'm not going to Punchy's wedding
炫耀一本杂志
to brag about a magazine...
虽然封面人物是我
cover.
巴尼  他不需要你的约会建议
Barney, he doesn't need dating advice from you.
你至今还不敢给诺拉打电话呢
You never even called Nora.
孩子们  你们还记得诺拉吧
Kids, you remember Nora.
可就在前几天
But just the other day...
-我晚点打给你  -从来不会太晚  巴尼
- I'll call you. - It's never too late, Barney.
还是你已经打了
Or did you call her?
我才不关心呢  打了吗
Not that I care. Did you?
我真不关心  到底打没打
I don't care. Did you?
其实我还没打
I haven't called her.
-伙计  -该死  巴尼
- Buddy. -Damn it, Barney.
我可是打从心底由衷真心希望你们在一起
I was really, really, really rooting for you two.
谁要吃辣鸡翅
Who wants hot wings?
我要
I'm in.
要不直接往巴尼身上泼辣酱吧
Or maybe we should just pour hot sauce on Barney,
因为他就是只畏畏缩缩的小鸡仔[胆小鬼]
since he's a total chicken.
我哪有临阵退缩
I did not chicken out.
诺拉是在寻求真爱
Nora is looking for something serious.
而我不是  所以没戏
I'm not. End of story.
还有  罗宾  我想来点鸡翅
And yes, Robin, I would love some wings.
吃本家没良心
Cannibal.
好吧  下一轮我买单
Okay, next round's on me.
-不  不  我们够了  -不  不
- Oh, no, we got it. - No, no...
莉莉和马修刚发现
Now Lily and Marshall had just found out
他们有宝宝了
they were having a baby.
-我要马上宣布这个好消息  -宝贝  不行
- I can't wait to tell everyone. - Baby, no,
头三个月我们要保密
We can't tell anyone. Not until three months.
有种说法怀孕头三个月  肚子里的宝宝不想让别人知道  不然可能会流产
我可不想坏事
I don't want to jinx it.
你有点过于迷信了吧
That's a bit superstitious, don't you think?
是谁每次登机  都要舔一下飞机
Whenever we board a flight, you lick the plane.
那我们飞机失事过吗
Have we crashed even once?
总之在确保顺利前一个字都别提  好吗
Don't say a word until we know everything's okay. Deal?
好吧  但我知道一切都会无比顺利的
Deal. But everything's just going to be great.
我保证
I promise.
你怎么保证
How can you guarantee that?
过来
Come here.
我开心极了  我不知道
I'm just so happy. I don't know how
这三个月要怎么做才能不被人发现
we're going to keep this secret for three months.
别紧张  瞒天过海很简单
Relax. It'll be easy.
你们要什么
What'll you have?
四杯啤酒  外加一杯不含酒精的
Four beers, plus one non-alcoholic.
你怀孕了  让我抱抱准妈咪
You're pregnant! Get in here!
然后我们就出发回我老家
And so we all headed to my hometown
去庆祝小粉拳的大日子
where we planned to celebrate Punchy's big day.
而巴尼叔叔则有其它计划
Uncle Barney had different plans.
准备好啦  克里夫兰
Get ready, Cleveland.
上一个像这样把你们搞得屁滚尿流
The last man to screw you this hard
然后消失无踪的是勒布朗・詹姆斯
then disappear was LeBron James.
以前在克里夫兰骑士队  后来为了总冠军去迈阿密热火队
你要在这儿拐妞上床
You're trying to get laid here?
-怎么了  -天啊  巴尼
- What? - God, Barney,
今晚可是泰德那个烦死人朋友
tonight is a magical night
和无印象新娘的婚礼奇妙夜
between Ted's annoying friend and what's-her-face.
别太放肆
Have some respect.
这不是单纯的拐妞上床
This isn't just getting laid.
这是市场调研
This is market research.
我的传奇胜率是百分之八十三
You see, my legendary success rate of 83%...
应该是百分之十七  他总是颠倒是非黑白
17-- it's always the inverse.
绝不是偶然的
...doesn't happen by accident.
我对女人们上演的每一种戏码
Every single play I run on women
都被一丝不苟地实践过
has been meticulously field-tested.
运用克里夫兰
By weeding out
这种小型市场检测戏码的好坏
the bad plays in smaller markets like Cleveland,
才能知道哪种适用于纽约
I know which ones will work in New York.
比方说
For example,
今晚的首场演出是
tonight marks the inaugural flight
刚逃出来的嗜血屠夫
of the escaped manslaughterer.
逃逸的嗜血屠夫销魂吧
Are escaped manslaughterers sexy?
-差远了  -逊弊了
- Not even remotely. - No. No.
完全正确  但只有当我亲身实践才知道真假
Exactly. We'll never know unless I try it out tonight.
尿斯比
Schmosby! Oh!
便便脸  大家好啊
Turd-faces! What's up?!
这戒指真咯得慌
You really feel that ring now.
真高兴你们都来了
So glad you all made it.
免费酒吧  干杯  便便脸
Open bar. Drink up, turd-faces,
这全入凯莉的爸爸的帐
'cause Kelly's dad's paying for all this,
而且他恨我入骨哦
and he hates my guts.
没错
It's true.
谁来拼酒  赶紧  来吧
Who's doing shots? Come on, let's go.
不了  谢谢
Oh, no, thank you.
你是怀孕了  还是怎么了
What are you pregnant or something?
不醉无归
Let's get hammered!
你今晚可是一人喝两人份  亲爱的
You're drinking for two tonight, baby.
我会为了我们的孩子而战
I will do this for the child.
-布朗队万岁  -布朗队万岁
- Go Browns! - Go Browns!
那是全美橄榄球联赛
In AFC regular season play,
如果他们说超级碗  你就要说  维京人队加油
but if they mean the Super Bowl, go Vikings.
布朗队属克里夫兰  维京人队属马修的家乡明尼苏达
爽
Yowza!
逃逸的嗜血屠夫  不够销魂
Escaped manslaughterers-- not sexy.
尽管是事后诸葛
Although in hindsight,
但这个想法的确考虑得不够周全
that was kind of a flawed concept.
下一场  零号病人[头号传染源]
Next up, patient zero.
莉莉  今晚我们喝个痛快
Lily, we are getting sloshed tonight.
全靠你了  亲爱的
That's all you, baby.
再喝我就空腹喝四杯了
I'll be four shots in with no food.
九个月以后  老娘的阴道要挤出
In nine months, I'll be pushing
一个头像南瓜这么大的埃里克森宝宝
a pumpkin-headed Eriksen baby out of my hoo-ha.
我想这几杯小酒  老爸还是能搞定的吧
I think Papa can manage a few extra cocktails.
说得好
Well played.
真爽[非洲斯瓦西里语]
Hakuna Matata!
我  我得出去透透气
I, uh, I got to get some air.
孩子们  还记得我跟你说过
Kids, remember how I told you
马修把小粉拳婚礼毁了吗
Marshall ruined Punchy's wedding?
现在还没到时候
That wasn't it.
天啊  你看看他
God, will you look at that guy.
真希望巴尼能跟我重修旧好
I wish Barney were my boyfriend again.
还是算了吧
No, thanks.
等下  这是你说真话的腔调
Wait a minute. That's your truth voice.
我的什么
My what?
每次你想用笑话来掩盖真话
Whenever you're trying to pass something off as a joke
一笑而过时  就会用这种腔调
but it's actually profoundly true, you use that voice.
我真希望辣妹组合能复合
I wish the Spice Girls would get back together.
她们超赞的
They were awesome.
糟透了
The worst.
是我放的
That was me.
我完全没忍住
I totally cut one.
那个男的真差劲
That guy.
我爸寄来的生日礼物
Birthday present from my dad.
我真正想要的其实是
All I really want is for him
一句他爱我
to tell me that he loves me.
开玩笑的啦
Just kidding.
有这支笔就够了
This pen's enough.
不够不够
It's not enough.
完全够了
It's totally enough.
我的上帝啊
Oh, my God.
你对巴尼余情未了
You still have feelings for Barney.
承认吧  你对他余情未了
Admit it, you still have feelings for Barney.
你比我想象的更醉哎
You are drunker than I thought.
-你看他那傻样  -等下等下
- I mean,look at the guy. - Wait, wait, wait.
在你走之前  请完成以下调查
Before you go, please answer the following survey
好让我今后把到你的机率能更大点
to help me better bang you in the future.
为什么这次的戏码你不买账
What didn't work for you about this play?
A  你不相信
Did you A) not believe
我是吉尼斯世界纪录的保持者
I was a Guinness Book world record holder?
还是 B 这些指甲恶心到你了
or B) did the fingernails gross you out?
我好期待你的祝词啊  尿斯比
I can't wait for your toast, Schmosby.
是啊  水龙头要关不住啦
Yeah, here come the waterworks.
等下  你赞成我在你的婚礼崩溃大哭吗
Wait. You're rooting for me to melt down at your own wedding?
对  大家都翘首期盼呢
Yeah, everyone is.
还有一些芬兰来的新朋友
Plus a few new friends from Finland.
祝你好运  尿斯比
Hey, good luck, Schmos.
祝你好运  祝你好运
Good luck, good luck.
快拿着
Take it.
让他们知道你有多厉害
Show them how awesome you are.
要厚着脸皮宣传自己  一分耕耘
Shamelessly plug yourself, so you can shamelessly plug,
-一分收获  -我都说了
- let's say that. - I told you,
我不是来这儿炫耀的  好吧
I'm not here to brag, okay?
够了
That's it.
你太谦虚了
You're too polite to brag.
好吧
Well, fine.
让我来
Let me.
因为这世上只有一个人马修・埃里克森
Because the only person on Earth
比马修・埃里克森更爱泰德・莫斯比
who loves Ted Mosby more than Marshall Eriksen,
那就是喝醉的马修・埃里克森
is drunk Marshall Eriksen.
好戏上场
So game on.
孩子们  还记得我跟你们讲过
Kids, remember how I told you
马修毁了小粉拳和凯利的婚礼吗
Marshall ruined Punchy and Kelly's wedding?
现在也还没到那个时候
That wasn't it either.
我和巴尼努力过了  但还是分手告终
Barney and I tried and failed.
都过去两年了
That was two years ago.
我为什么还要重蹈覆辙
Why would I ever go down that road again?
这完全不合理
It wouldn't even make sense.
不是凡事都要求合理的  感觉是很奇妙的
It doesn't have to make sense. It's chemistry.
我的第六感向来对这种事很敏锐
Look, I've always had a sixth sense about these things.
再加上现在我怀孕了
And now that I'm pregnant...
我以大脑为子宫  孕育这个想法
with this idea in my mind-uterus,
我现在看得更清楚了
I see things even clearer.
巴尼和你对彼此的感觉
You and Barney have the kind of chemistry
-都没有消失殆尽  -真的吗
- that just doesn't go away.- Really?
那他为什么想要鼓捣所有会动的东西呢
Then why is he trying to LeBron anything that moves?
你不买账是因为
Did this not work for you
A  吸血鬼这招被人玩烂了
because A) vampires are played out,
或是B  同时宣称我还是FACEBOOK的创始人
or B) claiming that I also invented Facebook
这个谎有点扯太大了
was kind of a hat on a hat?
他是因为你  才没有给诺拉打电话
You're the reason he never called Nora.
也是因为你  他今晚才只有在这做市场调查
You're the reason he's only test-marketing tonight.
更是因为你  他总是故意把其他女人三振出局
And you're the reason he keeps striking out on purpose.
这就是爱情
Chemistry.
哇  泰德
Whoa! Ted!
《纽约》杂志封面上的人真是你吗
Is that really you on the cover of New York magazine?
你要说  是啊
Now, you say "yes""
-快别说了  -尿斯比
- Please stop. - Schmosby.
这个杂志讲的什么
What's this about a magazine?
没什么大不了的  克雷
You know what, Clay? It's no big deal.
我告诉你  这可是件大事啊
You know what? It is a big deal.
克雷  我朋友泰德正在设计一幢摩天大楼
Clay, my friend Ted is designing a skyscraper, Clay.
你最近都在干嘛呢  克雷
What have you been up to, Clay?
我还在汽车租凭公司上班
Well, I'm still working at the rental car company...
不错不错
Bravo, bravo, Clay.
有没有出版社想写一篇
Any major publications want to write an article
关于你汽车租凭公司的文章啊
on your sweet rental car gig?
没有
No, no articles.
我的生活很沉闷
My life's pretty dull.
我最近唯一的新闻是这个小家伙
I guess the only news is this little gal.
老天爷啊  快看这个小宝贝
Oh, my God, wook at the wittle baby.
她太可爱了
She is so cute.
我好想把她的小脚
All I want to do is put her little feet
放进我的嘴巴里
in my mouth.
你创造了这么一个可人儿
You've created something truly beautiful.
她是我的全部
She is my everything.
我觉得这也算见大事吧
I mean, it's kind of a big deal...
摩天大楼耶  对吧
the building, you know?
小家伙
Hey, little one.
这位小天使晚上不哭闹  都能一觉睡到天亮啦
So, this little angel's already sleeping through the night?
我设计这幢大楼时
I've had some sleepless nights...
试过彻夜未眠
designing this building.
这无任何象征意义
Nothing symbolic about that.
算了吧
Let it go.
我和巴尼对彼此没有任何感觉
There is no chemistry left between me and Barney.
我们早结束了
We're done.
真的吗  证明给我看  去告诉他
Oh really? Prove it. Go tell him.
我为什么要去告诉他这个
Why would I go tell him that?
即便现在巴尼还没有意识到  但在内心深处
Because deep down, even if he isn't aware of it himself,
他是想和你在一起的
Barney wants to be with you.
如果你们不可能
And if it's not gonna happen,
他理应知道结果
he deserves to know.
好吧
Fine.
巴尼  一切都显而易见
Barney, just so everything is crystal clear...
我知道你要说什么
I know what you're gonna say.
我们要用行动  秀给克利夫兰看
Let's show Cleveland how it's done.
Deee Lite 《Groove is in the heart》
你溅落在我背上的冰水 *
* The chills that you spill up my back
让我心满意足 *
* Leave me filled with satisfaction
我们结束后  结果甚为满意 *
* When we're done, satisfaction of what's to come
我别无他求 *
* I couldn't ask for another
现在的我  别无他求 *
* Now I couldn't ask for another
心花怒放 *
* Groove is in the heart
一  二  三
One, two, three
心花怒放 *
* Groove is in your heart
* Groove is in the heart
心花怒放 *
巴尼...  我...
Barney... I...
抱歉
Sorry.
我的天  是诺拉
Oh, my God, it's Nora.
诺拉终于回我电话了
Nora's finally calling me back.
等等  你说你没打给她
Wait, you said you never called her.
我撒谎了  我打了  大概五次吧
I lied. I called her, like, five times.
等等
Wait, wait!
我超不会处理这种状况  这点你是最清楚的了
You of all people know how much I suck at these things.
你一定要帮我  求你了
You gotta help me. Please?
这是我第一次
Just once I would like
想认真做好一件事
to see what it feels like to not screw things up.
好吧
Yeah, mm-hmm.
好的
Okay.
诺拉  谢谢你回我电话
Hey, Nora. Thanks for calling me back.
你好  那个  我打给你
Um, hey, hi. The-the-the reason that, um,
是为了...
I called is, uh...
告诉你我对你的感觉
To tell you how I feel about you.
...to tell you how I feel about you.
虽然第一次我们以分手告终
I know we didn't work out the first time...
而我知道那并不能说明什么
...and I know it doesn't make any sense...
但我们是属于彼此的  这个想法在我心中挥之不去
...but I can't shake the feeling that we belong together.
但我们是属于彼此的
...but I can't shake this feeling
这个想法在我心中挥之不去
that we belong together.
你是否愿意再给我一次机会
Is there any part of you that wants to try again?
亲爱的  我憋不住了
Baby, I can't take it anymore.
我好想告诉大家你怀孕了
I've gotta tell somebody that we're pregnant.
埃里克森  坚持住
Eriksen, stay strong.
我们要死守这个秘密
We're keeping this secret.
到处都是孩子
There's babies everywhere.
处处充满着童趣
It's like a minefield of cuteness.
看看这个小混蛋
Look at this little bastard.
马修  停  坚持住
Marshall, stop it. Stay strong.
你不能这样抱小宝宝
You can't let holding some, some little baby...
看他可爱的的小嫩颊
oh, with the cute little cheeks
他的小藕臂
and the... the little arms
还有小粉腿
and little legs...
这个小混蛋还有膝盖窝
This son of a bitch has knee dimples.
快向众人宣布我怀孕了
Let's go tell everyone I'm pregnant.
好
Yeah!
你没事吧
You okay?
没事  你呢
Nope. You?
不太好
Not excessively.
要聊聊吗
You want to talk about it?
打死也不说
Not even a little.
说出来可能会好受些
Might make you feel better.
好的  这样吧
Okay, fine, I'll make you a deal:
你先说  而我
you go first,and then
则坚持打死也不说
I'll stick with my thing about not talking about it.
好的
Okay.
我的高中同学
All my friends from high school,
都有了美妻娇儿
they're here with their wives, their kids.
我呢  整晚只有奶乎乎的杂志作伴
Me? My date for the night is a sticky magazine.
听起来像是高中再现
Sounds like high school all over again.
抱歉  对着杂志打飞机脏的也是那块儿
Sorry, it was right there.
曾经的我相信命运
I used to believe in destiny, you know?
我去买百吉饼  见到一位漂亮女生在排队
I'd go to the bagel place, see a pretty girl in line
她看着我最爱的小说  哼着一首
reading my favorite novel, whistling the song
在我脑中萦绕一周挥之不去的小曲  我会想
that's been stuck in my head all week and I'd think,
老天  没准她就是我的真命天女
"Wow. Hey, maybe she's the one."
而现在的我则想  我就知道那个贱人
Now I think, "I just know that bitch is gonna take
会买走所有剩下的全麦百吉饼
the last whole-wheat everything bagel."
你只是太专心工作了
You've just been focused on work.
不  比这还糟
No, it's more than that.
我心中的信念之火已灭
I've stopped believing.
不是以那种极度消沉
Not in some depressed,
在致辞时大哭一场的方式
"I'm gonna cry during my toast" Way.
而是潜移默化的  直到我今晚才真正意识到
Not in a way I even noticed until tonight.
日复一日  我心中的信念之火越来越暗
It's just, every day, I think I believe a little less
火光微乎其微  最终暗淡无光
and a little less and a little less.
这感觉  好糟糕
And that... sucks.
我该怎么办  特布罗斯基
What do I do about that, Scherbatsky?
你是泰德・莫斯比
You're Ted Mosby.
你会重燃信念之火
You start believing again.
信什么  命运吗
In what, destiny?
感觉
Chemistry.
有了感觉  再加一样就大功告成
If you have chemistry, you only need one other thing.
是什么
What's that?
机缘
Timing.
可惜机缘可遇不可求
But timing's a bitch.
我们的四十之约还有效吗
Hey, we still have our 40 deal, right?
如果我们四十时都还单身...
If we're both still single at 40...
我绝对嫁给你
I'm all yours. Hmm
随便问问  建筑师能赚大钱吗
Unrelated, do architects make big money?
来势汹汹的都不是大钱
Aggressively medium money.
亏了
Damn it.
尿斯比  两分钟后上场
Schmosby, you're up in two minutes.
答应我两件事
Okay, promise me two things,
第一  重燃信念之火
One, you start believing again,
第二  不准在致辞时哭  尿斯比
And two, don't cry during the toast, Schmosby.
我保证
I promise.
很好
Good.
我怀孕了
We're having a baby.
真的吗
What, for real?
真的
For real.
各位请注意
Attention, everyone!
我们今晚齐聚一堂  就是为了此刻
It's time for the reason we're all here tonight.
欢迎尿斯比致辞
Schmosby's toast!
今晚我们欢聚  是为了歌颂爱情
We're here tonight to celebrate love.
爱情为我们带来新的生命
Love brings us new life...
你们
Hey!
这不是情绪崩溃
This isn't a meltdown.
这是喜极而泣
These are tears of joy.
泰德为他的朋友们开心
Ted is happy for his friends
他是我认识的最好的人
'cause he's the best guy that I know.
知道他为什么开心吗
And do you know why he's happy?
因为这位天仙怀孕了
Because this beautiful lady right here is pregnant.
你怎么知道的
How did you know that?!
这是个秘密
That was supposed to be a secret!
原来
Turns out...
布朗队万岁
Go Browns!
Go Browns! Whoo!
那是全美橄榄球联赛
In AFC regular season play,
如果他们说超级碗  你就要说  维京人队万岁
but if they mean the Super Bowl, go Vikings.
你真是色胆包天
How dare you.
你居然让她带球结婚  你这个人渣
That's my daughter, you piece of garbage.
您老还愿意为婚礼买单不
You're still gonna pay for all this, right?
你居然叫我儿子"人渣"
"Piece of garbage"? That's my son.
马修就是这样毁了小粉拳的婚礼
And that is how Marshall destroyed Punchy's wedding.
可我们不在乎
But we didn't care.
因为我们的小家庭要迎来第六位成员了
There was gonna be a sixth member of our little family.
再也不会有婚礼那么糟糕了  是吧
No wedding will ever, ever be as bad as that one, right?
我选择了正确的领带  对吗
I picked the right tie, didn't I?
太正确了
You nailed it.
总之不要是小鸭领带就行
And hey, just be glad it's not the ducky tie.
小鸭领带
Ooh, the ducky tie.
这可是个好故事  我会讲到的
That's a good story kids. I'll get to that.
老天爷  咱离大结局还早着呢
Man, we are not even close to the end.
你是个很棒的伴郎  泰德
You're a good best man, Ted.
婚礼念祝词时你会哭的  是吧
You're gonna cry during the toast, aren't you?
一定哭得稀里哗拉
Oh, I'm totally gonna cry.
进来
Come in.
泰德  新娘要见你
Ted, the bride wants to see you.
好的
Okay.
不是吧  你就戴这条领带吗
Really? You're gonna go with that tie?